<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scottish 6 Days</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scottish 6 Days</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>/bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bulletin/</guid>
      <description> Welcome to the Scottish Six Days </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 (UKOL)</title>
      <link>/news/day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_1/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 28th July
Auchingarrich
Organising Clubs: MAROC, AYROC, TINTO
Organisers: Sue Barrie &amp;amp; Paul Chapman (MAROC)
Planners: Dan Gooch &amp;amp; Scott Reynolds (MAROC)
Controllers: Donald Grassie (MOR) &amp;amp; Bob Sheridan (MAROC)
Day 1Directions: Follow A822 south over Crieff Bridge then turn right onto unclassified road. Follow 8km to turn left into parking field. Parking: Large sloping field immediately off the minor public road. ALL cars to arrive by 12: and NO exit before 12:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>/news/day_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_2/</guid>
      <description>Mon 29th July Edinchip Organising Clubs: MOR, ECKO, SOLWAY, STAG
Organisers: Carol Burnapp &amp;amp; Jan Kersel (ECKO) Planners: Roo Hornby &amp;amp; Ade Chapman (MOR)
Controllers: Richard Oxlade (ESOC) &amp;amp; Fredrik Nordvall Forsberg (STAG)
Day 2Directions: Access directly from the A85 at the T-junction with the A84 in Lochearnhead village. There are three possible approaches using the A85 west from Crieff, the A85 south from Crianlarich or A84 north from Callander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 (WRE)</title>
      <link>/news/day_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_3/</guid>
      <description>Tues 30th July
Dundurn &amp;amp; Cnoc a’ Mhadaidh
Organising Clubs: ESOC, BASOC Organisers: Tyler Morrison (ESOC) &amp;amp; Jo Cumming (BASOC)
Planners: Peter Halling (ESOC) &amp;amp; Duncan Francis (BASOC)
Controllers: David Esson (GRAMP), Roger Scrutton (ESOC) &amp;amp; Rob Hickling (BASOC)
Day 3Directions: Signposted from A85, east end of St. Fillans. Turn onto South Loch Earn Rd, cross narrow bridge (take care) and bear left at road bend. ALL cars to arrive by 12:00 and NO exit before 12:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>/news/day_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_4/</guid>
      <description>Thurs 1st August
Culteuchar &amp;amp; Dron
Organising Clubs: CLYDE, INT, EUOC, AROS Organisers: Rachel Wilson (CLYDE), Jane Carcas &amp;amp; Lucy Galloway (INT)
Planners: Max Carcas &amp;amp; Robin Galloway (INT)
Controllers: Brian Porteous (FVO) &amp;amp; Paul Caban (INT)
Day 4Directions: All traffic should approach from Perth to avoid a dangerous crossing of the A9. From A9/B934 junction, go south east on B934. After 2km and just after the level- crossing, bear left onto B935 to Forgandenny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 (WRE)</title>
      <link>/news/day_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_5/</guid>
      <description>Fri 2nd August
Craig a Barns
Organising Clubs: TAY, INVOC, ELO
Organisers: Fiona Downie &amp;amp; Jane Anderson (TAY)
Planners: Dave Summers &amp;amp; Kevin Holliday (INVOC)
Day 5Controllers: Trevor Hoey (FVO), Ted Finch (FVO) &amp;amp; Paul Caban (INT)
Directions: Due to ongoing works (dualling of the A9) and safety considerations (cars stacking back onto the A9), all vehicles should access the area from the south through Dunkeld (recommended route from Crieff is via Aberfeldy, A827 to Ballinluig then south on A9 to A signposted for Dunkeld).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6 (UKOL)</title>
      <link>/news/day_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/day_6/</guid>
      <description>Sat 3rd August
Grandtully
Organising Clubs: GRAMP, KFO, RR
Organisers: Sam Gomersall &amp;amp; Lesley Gomersall (GRAMP)
Planners: Pete Lawrence &amp;amp; Zoe Griffin (GRAMP)
Controllers: Andy Oliver (MAROC) &amp;amp; Simon Gardner (CLYDE)
Day 6Directions: From the North or the South take the A9 to Ballinluig, then take the A827 towards Aberfeldy for approx 6km. The event parking is at the junction of the A827 and the B898. Parking: Large flat field off the B898.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving in Strathearn</title>
      <link>/news/driving_in_strathearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/driving_in_strathearn/</guid>
      <description>Please obey all road safety notices and signs. Remember to drive on the left hand side! All the days have more than one possible route of approach. The map shows location of main event signage off the trunk and local roads. Routes have been agreed with the local authority and police. Please be patient if queues build up entering or leaving the parking fiel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Medical Information</title>
      <link>/news/emergency_medical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/emergency_medical/</guid>
      <description>In Emergency: dial 999 or 112
NHS 24: dial 111
A&amp;amp;E: Perth Royal Infirmary, PH1 1NX, Telephone: 01738 623311, or Forth Valley Royal Hospital, Stirling Rd, Larbert FK 4WR
Minor Injuries Unit: Crieff Community Hospital, PH7 3HR, Telephone: 01764 653173</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Health Matters</title>
      <link>/news/general_health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/general_health/</guid>
      <description>Ticks Ticks are common in the competition areas. Check carefully after each run and remove any (the recommended method is using an O’Tom Tick Twister). Lyme disease does also occur in the area; if you develop a rash at the site of a tick bite, you are advised to seek medical advice.
Tick Project: TickApp (a citizen science project run by SRUC and University of Edinburgh) will be attending (Day 1 and 3) to compare the number of ticks collected using survey transects (scientific method) with the number of ticks reported by people after orienteering in the same area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Information</title>
      <link>/news/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/general/</guid>
      <description>Bio-security: Please use the shoe baths EVERY day. Clean paws, shoes and wheels after EVERY day to control the spread of forest diseases. One of our areas has recently been affected by Phytophthora Ramorum (a tree pathogen) – please strictly obey OOB signs.
Waste: Rubbish and Recycling bins will be provided in the Arenas. Please use them and leave no litter at all. The plastic tape used as Lace Tape is NOT biodegradable, please ensure you take away your pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>/news/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration is at Morrison’s Academy, Ferntower Rd, Crieff, PH7 3AN.
Registration will be from 12:00-18:00 on Saturday 27th July. Bibs, hired SI cards, programmes, bus passes and pre- ordered merchandise may be collected. General information will be available at the Event Centre on registration day and thereafter at each event Arena. There will be traders but no food providers. Crieff has a good selection of local cafes within walking distance of Morrison’s Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shuttle Bus</title>
      <link>/news/shuttle_bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/shuttle_bus/</guid>
      <description>For pre-booked passengers only. The timetable is available at Information and on the website. The bus pick up points will be Comrie Croft and Victoria Terrace beside Morrison’s Academy, Crieff; with a limited pickup from Twenty Shilling Caravan Park (Tullybannocher Cafe).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Programme</title>
      <link>/news/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/social/</guid>
      <description>Tickets for sale at Registration on Sat 27th July and each day in assembly field at Enquiries/ Information (until all tickets sold).
Sun 28th July 19:30-20:30 Scottish Landscapes - scenic slide show by Crieff-based landscape photographer Annette Forsyth. Entry by donation to cover costs (excess to charity). Venue : Morrison’s Academy, Ferntower Hall, Ferntower Rd, Crieff, PH7 3AN.
Sun 28th July 18:00-19:00 Exclusive tour of Drummond Castle Gardens (as featured in TV show Outlander) by Fiona Downie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint - Crieff West</title>
      <link>/news/sprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/sprint/</guid>
      <description>Venue: Macrosty Park and Crieff West.
Organising Clubs Masterplan Adventure
Organiser: Chris Smithard (MA).
Planner: Graham Gristwood (MA)
Controller: Bill Stevenson (ESOC).
Parking In the playing fields, Turretbank Road, Crieff (PH7 4LJ).
Area adjacent to the parking and Macrosty Park
Start Times: 10:30-13:30. SI timing (including Touch Free).
Map: ISSOM 1:4,000 (courses 1&amp;amp;2), 1:3,000 (courses 3-7), 2.5m contours. Surveyed and drawn October 2018 by G Gristwood.
Ter rain: Mixture of runnable (but detailed) parkland with some steep slopes and a hilly urban area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trail O (Drummond Castle)</title>
      <link>/news/trailo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:19:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/trailo/</guid>
      <description>Organiser: Anne Hickling (ESOC).
Controller: Rob Hickling (BASOC).
Planner: Roger Scrutton (ESOC)
Venue: Drummond Castle, 4 miles south of Crieff off A822.
Parking: In a field just beyond Drummond Castle.
Start times: 12:00-14:00. No allocation of start times.
Map: 1:4,000, 2011 map by Stirling Surveys, updated for TrailO by Rob Hickling, May 2019.
Courses: One course only, with 5 TempO and 8 PreO stations (subject to final controlling). The course will be along good tracks, suitable for wheelchairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Lengths and Climbs</title>
      <link>/news/course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/course/</guid>
      <description>Strathearn 2019 &amp;ndash; Provisional Course lengths &amp;amp; climbs Data correct as of 4th July 2019
  Course
  Day 1
 Day 2  Day 3
 Day 4  Day 5
  Day 6
      Auchingarrich
  Edinchip
  Dundurn &amp;amp; Cnoc a’Mhadaidh
  Culteuchar &amp;amp; Dron
  Craig a’Barns
 Grandtully   1
  1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>